Finding Aid for the Colin Higgins papers, ca. 1960-1987 LSC.1560
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Colin Higgins - Personal
  - Speaking engagements / interviews, 1986. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Speaking engagements / interviews, 1984, 1985. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Speaking engagements / interviews, 1983. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - General background interviews. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Montreal visit, - visiting artist., February 1982 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Montreal Film Festival, (2 folders)., 1982 (Box 67, Folder 10, 11)
  - Interviews and articles, 1981-1982. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Nine to Five - Colin Higgins interviews. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Interviews /speaking engagements, 1987. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Interviews and speaking engagements. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Australia / New Zealand interviews. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Early interviews. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Christopher Isherwood. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Don Johnson. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - [Article on Lew Wasserman, Double Page, February 1982]. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Olympics., 1984 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1984. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, 1979. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Obituaries. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Party file. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Past lives ()., April 1985 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Directors Guild memorial. (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Photographs. (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Photographs. (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Photographs [in magazines]. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Players Club. (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Political. (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Producers Guild of America, Incorporated. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Radiance - Dorothy Fadiman. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Film retrospectives. (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Mickey Rooney - sixty years. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Schedule, 1986. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Schedule, 1985. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Schedule, 1984. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Daily schedule, 1983. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Daily schedule, 1982. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Daily schedule, 1981. (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Daily schedule, 1980. (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Weekly schedule, January 1, 1979-. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Weekly schedule, April 1-December 31, 1978. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Actor - Into the Night ()., 1984 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Syd Field's Screenplay - 2 copies. (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Scripts donated. (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Hutton Drive security (Westec). (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Society of Stage Directors (directory) and Choreographers. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Personal stationery. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Hutton Drive - miscellaneous. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Hutton Drive additions, 1985. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - House addition, 1982. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - House addition, 1982. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Green Valley Road, 1981. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - [Notes - Montreal Exposition, ?]., 1967 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - [UCLA course notes]. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Lab books and editor. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Gandhi - post-production script. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - [Equipment catalogs]. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Mo Pix dealers - rental catalogues. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, prior to 1976. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Early contracts. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Franciscan Communications Center. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - The Phantom. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - The Bluebird. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Ziegler Associates, contract., 1976 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Lee Strasberg - master class in acting. (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Ralph Sergeant stuff. (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous movie clippings - trivia (2 folders). (Box 73, Folder 3, 4)
  - Colin Higgins - yearly. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - UCLA History of Film course - (Colin's notes as student); [empty - see Box 71 folder 10]. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous actors - interviews. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Sir Alec Guinness. (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Marcel Marceau. (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Sir Lawrence Olivier. (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Film music - composers. (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous directors - A-K. (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous directors - L-Z. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Ingmar Bergman. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Francis Ford Coppola. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Federico Fellini. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - John Ford. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Howard Hawks. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Alfred Hitchcock. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Stanley Kubrick. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Fritz Lang. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Claude Lelouch. (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - Sam Peckinpah. (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Roman Polanski. (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Otto Preminger. (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Jean Renoir. (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Ken Russell. (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - John Schlesinger. (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Joseph Von Sternberg. (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Preston Sturges. (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Slavko Vorkapich. (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - Orson Welles. (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - How to produce. (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous producers. (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous writers. (Box 74, Folder 23)
  - Neil Simon. (Box 74, Folder 24, 25)
  - Telephone book. (Box 74, Folder 26)
  - Theater seating diagrams. (Box 74, Folder 27)
  - Things to keep. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - American Airlines and United Airlines Mileage Club information. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - [Trips]. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Europe trip, October 1984. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Travel and resorts. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - UCLA Alumni. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - UCLA Colin Higgins Fellowship. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - UCLA Writers' Block. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Video file. (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Robert Wilson. (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Writers Guild of America. (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Colin Higgins Productions. (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Will. (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Variety - National Academy for Film Makers file. (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - American Cinematheque. (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Daily schedule, 1987/1987. (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - [Culver Military School]. (Box 94, Folder 13)
- Colin Higgins Productions
  - Photographs - Bungalow 424 - construction in progress. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Offices - producers #7 - Columbia Pictures. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Producers 7 - Offices - Computer print-outs - Columbia. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Expense reports. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous - Universal Productions, 1984. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous - Columbia Pictures, 1983. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Computer runs - office operating expenses. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Office operating expenses, 1988. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Office operating expenses, 1987. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Office operating expenses, 1986. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Office operating expenses, 1985. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Storeroom / Non-stock purchases, 1985. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Office operating expenses, 1984. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Payment requests, 1984. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Petty cash, [empty]., 1988 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Petty cash, [empty]., 1986 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Petty cash, [empty]., 1985 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Petty cash [empty]. (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Petty cash, [empty]., 1987 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Productions pending - studio lists. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Ratings - mini file. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Stores and purchase requisitions. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Universal stationery. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Warner Brothers. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Appliances. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - [Postcards]. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - [Accounts payable - various studios]. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Expense reports. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Outside submission correspondence, 1978-1982. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Outside correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Godmother productions submissions [empty]. (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Incoming and outgoing call register, October 29, 1984-September 6, 1985. (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Incoming and outgoing call register, February 3-October 26, 1984. (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, February 6-July 19, 1983. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, July 20, 1983-February 3, 1984. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, May 7, 1982 - February 8, 1983. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, June 16, 1980-February 5, 1981. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, October 17, 1979-June 13, 1980. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, May 5-October 6, 1979. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, July 14, 1978-March 2, 1979. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, December 5, 1977-July 13, 1978. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, August 3-December 2, 1977. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, March 28-August 2, 1977. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, July 30, 1981-May 6, 1982. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Bungalow 424 - construction. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Incoming and outgoing telephone calls, February 6-July 29, 1981. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Offices. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Columbia Pictures - deal. (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Arigo. (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Barbra and Goldie. (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Dixie. (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Dudley Moore movie. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Growing up in Australia. (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - NBC Reports: Oh, what a sorry war - The Falklands (script). (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Harold and Maude, Part 2. (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - To begin again - story and treatment by N. Frangakis, January 30, 1987. (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Louise Hay - documentary. (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Hay Foundation. (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Hitler's dentures (2 folders). (Box 77, Folder 18, 19)
  - Marsupial adventure. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Me and Uri ()., 1977 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Joan Rivers project - Me and the queen. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Mickey and Maude. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Bette Middler - Paris. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - When Colin goes to Hawaii. (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - When Colin goes to San Francisco. (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - When Colin goes to New York. (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - When Colin goes to England. (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - When Colin goes to France. (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - Pending. (Box 94, Folder 11)
- College
  - [Notes on Greeks, etc.]. (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - [English 1 essays]. (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - [Essays]. (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - [English 155 notes and essays]. (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - [Music 1, notes]. (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - [Art 1, notes]. (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - [English 143, Shakespeare - notes]. (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - [AF 160, Moliere - notes]. (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - [English 102, Old English - notes]. (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - [Sociology 1,notes]. (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - [English 182, English literature of the Rennaisance - notes]. (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - [English 183, Neoclassicism and romanticism - notes]. (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - [Enlglish 184, Victorian and modern English literature - notes]. (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - [French - notes]. (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - [School appointment calendars:, 1967-68 and 1969-70]. (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - [UCLA diploma, certificates, awards]. (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - [UCLA MFA records]. (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - [Modern history, ancient history - notes]. (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - [English classes - notes and essays]. (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - [Math, economics and religion - notes]. (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - [Physics - notes]. (Box 139, Folder 5)
- Columbia Office
  - [Plans, 33 items]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [Plans, 10 items]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence
  - [Correspndence ca., 1967-1970]. (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence ca., 1970-1974]. (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence ca. and ID cards - UCLA, Army etc]., 1971-1972 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, ca. 1971-1973]. (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, and ID cards - student, army]., ca. 1972-1974 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - [Correspondence, ca. 1965-1970]. (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, 1963-1975]. (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, ca. 1967]. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, ca. 1967-1973]. (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1977-1980 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1977-1980 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1977-1980 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1977-1980 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1977-1980 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1980-1983 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1977-1980 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - [Unarranged, ca. 1977-1980]. (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, ca. 1977-1980]. (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1980-1983 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1980-1983 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence ca., unarranged]., 1980-1983 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence ca., unarranged]., 1980-1983 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1983-1984 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1984 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1984 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1984 (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1984 (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1984 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1985 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged., ca. 1985 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1985 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1985 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1985 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1985 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1985 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1985 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1986 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1987 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1987 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1987 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1987 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - [Correspondence, unarranged]., ca. 1987 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - [Correspondence, ca. 1960(?)]. (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - [Correspondence, ca. 1964-1967]. (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - [Correspondence (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - [Correspondence, 1974]. (Box 135, Folder 27)
- Dangerous Paradise
  - Synopsis. (Box 77, Folder 1)
- The Day the Film Broke
  - [The Day the Film Broke, screenplay]. (Box 135, Folder 14)
- Death Knocks
  - [Death Knocks, script]. (Box 135, Folder 23)
- Desperadoes
  - [Synopsis]. (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Devil's Daughter
  - [Devil's Daughter, unbound typescript]. (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Devil's Daughter. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - [Devil's Daughter script, final draft,, with notes]., August 8, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - [Devil's Daughter script, first draft, August 1, 1972]. (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - [Devil's Daughter script, revised first draft, August 8, 1972]. (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - [Devil's Daughter, final shooting script, October 17, 1972]. (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - [Devil's Daughter script, second draft, ]; Signed by C. Higgins, His mark, his script., August 19, 1972 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - [Devil's Daughter, story outline. (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - [Devil's Daughter, story outline]. (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - [Devil's Daughter, script notes, ABC]. (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - The Devil's Daughter - script - bound,; Final shooting script interleaved with stills., January 9, 1973 (Box 133, Folder 1)
- Early Career
  - Overdue nightly contracts. (Box 134, Folder 8)
- Emotion
  - Third draft videoplay, - Richard Baskin., October 1, 1984 (Box 81, Folder 6)
- Ephemera
  - Memo and note from James Rogers, - ephemera., 1984 and 1986 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - [Posters - Foul Play, 9-5, Harold and Maude]. (Box 141, Folder 1)
- Flasher
  - Rewrite version w/Michael Haller, February 2, 1981. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - 1st draft by Lawrence J. Cohen and Fred Freeman, 1972. (Box 56, Folder 9)
- Florie
  - [Florie, #2 description]; Typescript with holograph corrections and professor's corrections. (Box 135, Folder 7)
- Foul Play
  - Press Kit (4 folders). (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
  - [3 posters]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [HMS Pinafore, 4 stage plans]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Weekly production costs. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Production notes. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Programs. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Production reports - 1st and 2nd units. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Props. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Publicity. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pre-release press clippings. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Radio interviews. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Colin Higgins interviews. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - MPAA ratings. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Release schedule. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Research. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Reviews. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Press. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Reviews. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Screenings. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Premiere - and screenings list. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Award screenings. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Killing Lydia aka Foul Play. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Writer's draft, February 3, 1977. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Screenplay, with looseleaf notes., August 10, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Screenplay - first draft. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Screenplay. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Screenplay, September 20, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Screenplay - final draft,; With loose pp.103-121., September 23, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Screenplay - final draft, - #209., September 23, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Screnplay - final draft, September 23, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Screenplay - final draft, - #213., September 23, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Screenplay - final draft, - #208., September 23, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Screenplay - final draft, September 23, 1977. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Screenplay - final draft,; With revised pages, September 23, 1977 October 17, 1977. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Screenplay - final draft,; With revisions of, September 23, 1977 October 17, 1977. (Box 4, Folder 4-8)
  - Release dialogue script, - #31116; 3 copies., August 21, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
  - Old Foul Play pages and notes. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pre-release advertising. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Advertising. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sneak-preview advertisements. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Audit. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Academy Award nominations. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Awards and film festivals. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Golden Globes. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Budget. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Call sheets - 1st and 2nd units. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Actors we've seen and casting session lists. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Casting. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - San Francisco casting. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Cast deal memos. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Staff and crew list. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Deal. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Day-out-of-days. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Earnings. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Editing. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Editing - the chase. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Educational film strip. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Colin Higgins - expenses. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Foreign reviews and openings. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Australia - opening. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - French dialogue. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gag letter (New Zealand). (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Gag M/M gift. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Letters. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Locations. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Looping. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Paramount marketing meeting. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Music. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Paperback novelization. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photographs. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Post-production. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Previews. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Daily progress reports. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Porno film. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Newscast copy. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Original of Script Supervisor's script - with photographs; Marie Kenney's copy, heavily annotated. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Screenplay - with production notes - photocopy; Production schedule, wild track list, revised pages ... (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Script notes, - Marie Kenney - #143; Heavily annotated., September 23, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Shooting schedule (including pre-production). (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - 16 mm print for Colin Higgins. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Television file. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Television special - A weekend of Foul Play. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Television showings. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Main and end titles. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Video cassettes. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - [Foul Play, shooting schedule]. (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - [Foul Play, production script (?)]. (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - [Foul Play, production notes, etc.]. (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - [Foul Play, bound scrapbook]. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - [Foul Play, photo album]. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - [Foul Play script,, no.121]., August 10, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - [Foul Play script, Not the final script, I made changes...]; ...changes throughout incl. making Stanley the conductor.. (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - [Foul Play script, final draft, no.252]., September 23, 1977 (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - [Foul Play, writer's draft, February 3, 1977]. (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Killing Lydia, first draft completed, October 12, 1971. (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - [Killing Lydia, second draft]. (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - [Killing Lydia script, original, no. 1]. (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - [Foul Play, research notes]. (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - [Foul Play, research notes on killings]. (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - [Foul Play, research notes, religion and the church]. (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - [Foul Play, notes and research for plot, title, etc.]; Ideas and notes on past thrillers.. (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco and Miss Haverstock [research for Foul Play]. (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - 3. The anthropologist. (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Who'd want to kill Miss Haverstock script. (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - [Foul Play, research notes]. (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - [Foul Play, research material]. (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - [Foul Play script, final draft, September 23, 1977]. (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - [Foul Play script]. (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - [Foul Play, first treatment]. (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - [Foul Play script]. (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - [Foul Play script, writer's draft, January 31, 1977]. (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - [Foul Play script, writer's draft, February 3, 1977]. (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - [Foul Play, outline]. (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - 20 items (folder 1 of 4). (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - 20 items. (Box 146, Folder 2-4)
  - Laser video disk. (Box 147, Folder 2)
- Frankie Appleseed
  - Marijuana movie. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Marijuana movie research articles. (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Marijuana movie research - pamphlets. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Marijuana movie research - books. (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Gang on 42nd Street
  - [The Gang on 42nd Street]; Typescript with holograph corrections. (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - [The Gang on 42nd Street, part one]. (Box 135, Folder 17)
  - [The Gang on 42nd Street, script]; Typescript with corrections/comments. (Box 135, Folder 29)
- The Geistlichshön Girl
  - [The Geistlichshön Girl, #3 dialog]; typescript with professor's comments. (Box 135, Folder 8)
- The Girl in the Winter
  - [The girl in the winter, screenplay idea]. (Box 135, Folder 35)
- Gladys and Anita
  - Background. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - A killer weekend - chicanos and gangs. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 77, Folder 7)